Guide to the Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Papers MSS.642
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Personal, 1888-2023; 1950-2000; 25 Linear Feet in 39 manuscript boxes, 2 small flat boxes, 4 oversize flat boxes, and 1 flat-file folder; 472.91 Megabytes in 441 computer files
  - Subseries I.A. Edie Windsor, circa 1900s-2023; 17.80 Linear Feet in 24 manuscript boxes and 5 oversized flat boxes.
    - Family -- Edmund "Blackie" Schlain (Brother), 1940-1992
      - Correspondence, 1943-1945, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Photographs, 1940-1943, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Family -- Eric, Jeremy "Remy", and Jon Rieder (Nephews) Correspondence, 1951-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
    - Family -- Family Members' Photographs, circa 1900s-1960s (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Family -- James "Jack" Schlain (Father), 1958
      - Estate Material (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Photographs and Negatives of Edie and Jack (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Family -- Maya (Cousin) Booklet, "My Cousin Edie", circa 2013 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Family -- Sonya "Sunnie" (Cousin) Photographs with Her Family and Edie, 2013, circa 2013-2017 (Box 59, Folder 16-17)
    - Friends -- Candid and Posed Photographs, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Fun Home Broadway Show -- Edie's Article, Show Tickets, and Related, 2015 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Funeral / Memorial Service Program, Guestbook, and Related, 2017 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Gift -- Booklet on Managing Finances, Created by Edie for Willie Spyer, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Greece Trips -- Travel Documents, 1965-2005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Health and Wellness -- Diet Tracking Material, 1962-1990s (Box 18, Folder 7-9)
    - Health and Wellness -- Smoke Enders Material, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Health and Wellness -- Spa Promotional Material, 1970-1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Health and Wellness -- Jacqueline Rogers' Life Control Institute Informational Material, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Health and Wellness -- Diet Program Chart, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Historical Landmarks Cultural Medallion / Plaque-Related, and Walking Map and Tour Directions, 2018-2019 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor and Edie Photographs, circa 2015-2017 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - List of Edie's Favorite Lesbian Bars, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Lorraine Hansberry Documentary Project Release Forms, 2016 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Marriage to Saul Wiener (Windsor), 1940s-1950s, circa 2000s
      - Forms and Documentation, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Photographs, 1940s-1950s, circa 2000s (Box 60, Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Wedding Reception Photograph, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Marriage to Judith Kasen Documents, September 26, 2016 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Marty Cohen and Edie at the Beach Photograph, circa 1947-1951 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - New York City Department of Education Poster Illustration of Edie, 2018 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - New York City Department of Parks Passes with Photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Notebooks and Notes, 1970s-2016 (Box 19, Folder 1-11, Box 20, Folder 1-8)
    - Party for Paula Photographs, January 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Passports, 2002-2012 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) -- Family, Friends, Soldier Friends, 1941-1947 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) -- Family, Friends, College, Beach, 1946-1948 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) -- Family, Friends, Beach, Travel, 1951-1955 (Box 58, Folder 9-11)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) and Negatives -- Trips to Provincetown and Nantucket, Girlfriend Selma, Beach, Friends, 1955-1957 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) and Negatives -- Family, Friends, Trips, Beach, June-July 1958 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) and Negatives -- Friends, Trips, Beach, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) and Negatives -- Friends, Family, New Year's Party, 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Photograph Album (Deconstructed) and Negatives -- Beach, Friends, Family, Parties, June-December 1963 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Poetry by Edie, circa 1950s (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Posed Photographs, circa 1960s (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Posed Photograph -- Edie Holding Diamond Circle Engagement Pin, circa 2009-2015 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Posed Photograph -- Edie in Her Office, circa 2010-2017 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Posed Photograph -- Edie Next to Photograph of Thea, circa 2010-2017 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Posed Photograph -- Edie at Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Site, circa 2012-2017 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Posed Photograph by Ryan Brandenberg, circa 2012-2017 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Posed Photograph by Max Vadukul, 2013 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Posed Photograph, September 2014 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Posed Photograph by B. Proud, 2014 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Posed Photographs, circa 2016-2017 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Song Lyrics and Sheet Music for Edie & Judith, by Dan Martin and Michael Biello, 2017 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Windsor-Spyer Trust, 2004, 2013, 2017 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
  - Subseries I.B. Thea Spyer, 1888-2009; 5 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 3 oversized flat boxes.
    This subseries documents the life of Thea Spyer, focusing primarily on her early childhood through early adulthood. There is a small amount of material on her later adult life.
    There are an extensive number of images of Spyer as an only child, growing up in the Netherlands in the 1930s where her father served in the Dutch military and also owned a successful pickling business. Early images include Thea's mother, Elisabeth, who died when she was only a few years old and later her stepmother, Jetty. Due to their Jewish heritage, Thea's family was forced in the late 1930s to escape to England and then eventually the family settled in the United States. Other images in this subseries include formal portraits and candid shots of Thea from the 1940s to mid-1950s. Family travel photographs from the 1950s capture trips through Europe with her father and stepmother. Later images include a January 1965 trip to Eleuthera with Thea's then-girlfriend before she started to date Edie Windsor. Images of Edie and Thea together are in Series I.C.
    Spyer's time as a Girl Scout at Camp Barree in the summer of 1947 is well-documented through brochures, photographs, and press clippings. School-related material in this subseries dates from the 1940s including class assignments, report cards, and graduation programs. Of note are concert programs from Spyer's time as a violin student in the Juilliard School of Music's Preparatory Division dating from the late 1940s to early 1950s. Her academic career is further represented through college-level class papers, correspondence, and student records from Sarah Lawrence College, the New School for Social Research, and Adelphi College.
    Early family history materials feature documentation of her father Willem Spyer's Dutch military service beginning in the early 1910s, as well as notes on the broader Spyer family history, specifically photographs of her family's pickle factory in the Netherlands. A small collection of correspondence between Spyer's family dating from the 1930s while her father was serving in the Dutch military is also in this subseries.
    Additional materials include Spyer's passports and citizenship papers; international driving certificate; jury summonses (with references to her multiple sclerosis); and life insurance forms and questionnaires.
    Spyer's 2009 death certificate, obituary, tributes, funeral arrangements, and a digital video recording of her memorial service are also in this subseries.
    - Address Book, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Candid Images of Thea, 1955-2009
      - Photographs, circa late 1950s-early 1960s (Box 60, Folder 7, Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, circa 1970s (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Slide Images -- Her Reading, and at New Year's Eve Party, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Photographs with Friends, circa 1980s (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, circa 1990s (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Photographs -- In Bed or in Wheelchair, circa 1990s-2009 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Photographs -- Getting a Haircut, April 1992 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Photograph, August 1994 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Childhood Photographs, circa 1931-1935
      - With Father and Mother, circa 1931-1933 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - With Father and Others, circa 1931-1933 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - On Boardwalk with Father and Others, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - With Father and Stepmother, circa 1934-1935 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Childhood Photographs, circa late 1930s-early 1940s
      - Playing, Casual Poses, Sports (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Brownie Troop Parade (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - Posed Portraits, circa 1931-1935 (Box 60, Folder 17, Box 76, Folder 5)
      - With Group, June 1935 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Posing Alone and with Others, September 1939 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Childhood Photographs -- Posing, Playing Violin, Riding Bike, with Father and Groups, circa 1940s (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence -- Addressed to Thea, Regarding Her Parents (in Dutch), 1933 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence -- Thea with Parents, 1933-1941 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1997 (Box 20, Folder 18-19)
    - Death, Burial, and Memorial Service, 2009
      - Death Certificate, Obituary, Tributes, Funeral Arrangements, Memorial Program (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Memorial Service -- Digital Video Recording, FA_MSS_642_ER_22
    - Education -- Middle Through High School Ephemera, 1940-1950 (Box 20, Folder 20-21)
    - Education -- Class Project: "From Windmills to Skyscrapers" Life Story by Thea, circa 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Education -- "News Club Scrapbook" Containing Articles by Thea, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Education -- Juilliard School of Music Preparatory Section Ephemera, 1947-1951 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Education -- Sarah Lawrence College -- Correspondence, Student Reports, and Father's Report, 1950-1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Education -- Down's Hospital Nursery School, 1952-1953
      - Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Photographs of Thea with Children and Co-Workers (Box 25)
    - Education -- New School for Social Research Student Record and Ephemera, 1952-1955 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Education -- Adelphi College Student Record and Related, 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Education -- Literature Class Paper, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Exercise Brochures, Booklets, and Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Family -- Elisabeth Spyer (Mother), 1888, 1927-1934, undated
      - Birth, Death, and Marriage Certificates and Related (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Photographs (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Family -- Spyer Family Pickle Factory Photographs, circa 1900-1930 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Family -- Willem Spyer (Father), 1911-1987
      - Dutch Military Service and Estate Documents (Box 21, Folder 11-12, Box 72, Folder 6, Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Photographs of Spyer in Uniform, Casual, and with First and Second Wives, Elisabeth and Judith (Box 60, Folder 28-29)
    - Family -- Thea's Notes on Family History, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Family -- Dick Spyer (Cousin) Photographs, 2001, 2006, undated (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Family -- Patsy Spyer Material, 2002, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Family and Friends with Thea Photographs, circa 1950s (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Friends and Thea Photographs, circa 1980s, September 1997 (Box 60, Folder 32-33)
    - Girl Scout Camp Barree, June-July 1947
      - Promotional Booklet, Correspondence, Press Clippings (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Camp Activities and Group Photographs (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - International Driving Permit, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Jury Summons Questionnaires, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Life Insurance Forms and Notes, 1976-1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Passports and Citizenship-Related Documents, 1940-2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Posed Portrait Images, 1950s-1970s
      - Posed Next to Flower Box, circa 1950s (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - Photographs, circa 1950s (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - Photographs, circa 1960s (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - Photographs, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - Photographs, 1973, 1970s (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Thea's Father's Day Gift Scrapbook, 1946-1949 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Travel -- Thea and Family Photographs, circa 1950s (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Travel -- Photographs from Italy, Monaco, and Switzerland, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Travel -- Photographs with Father in London, September 1950 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Travel -- Photographs with Thea and Others, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Travel -- Photographs Thea with Couple in Windsor, England, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Travel -- Photographs Thea with Father and Stepmother in Italy, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Travel -- Slide Images of Thea with Girlfriend Frederica in Eleuthera, Bahamas, January 1965 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Violin Authentication Papers, 1948-1988 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Subseries I.C. Household, 1953-2017; 12.80 Linear Feet in 15 manuscript boxes, 4 oversized flat boxes, and 1 flat-file folder.; 472.91 Megabytes in 441 computer files
    This subseries documents the over four-decade long relationship of Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer, a lesbian couple whose enduring partnership and eventual marriage offers a powerful lens into LGBTQ+ life in the second half of the 20th century and early 21st century. Living together in New York City and spending summers on Long Island, Edie and Thea navigated the typical challenges of a relationship while also contending with the realities of remaining closeted in their professional lives, and also constantly adjusting to the long-term progression of Thea's multiple sclerosis. Their life together, beginning in 1965, is extensively chronicled through images and materials which illustrate their vibrant social world, centered mostly within their LGBTQ+ community, featuring decades of gatherings, vacations, celebrations, and their day-to-day lives.
    Beginning in the late 1970s, Thea's slow progression of MS eventually rendered her a quadriplegic, requiring she use a wheelchair and full time care. Material in this subseries illustrates how the couple adapted to this loss of mobility through photographs and floorplans of accessibility-related renovations to their Fifth Avenue apartment and Tuckahoe Lane home, as well as manuals for mobility aids like bed and pool lifts. Notes and notebooks dating back to the 1970s through the early 2000s record reflections on Thea's diagnosis, symptoms, and care, as well as incidental documents, including jury duty summons for both women, which offer insight into how MS shaped their civic and personal lives.
    This subseries documents Edie and Thea's love of the beach and the Long Island area, which started early in their relationship. Photographs of their first summer house rental together in 1966, which they nicknamed: "Mrs. Fordham's" are in this subseries. Images include beach days, visitors, and alone time together. Photographs, slides, and albums from subsequent summers, especially at their Tuckahoe Lane home purchased in 1969, capture pool parties, visitors, and holidays with friends and family. For the rest of their lives together, their summers were split, driving between New York City and Southampton. This subseries also includes a large collection of casual and posed images of Edie and Thea taken from 1965 through Thea's death in 2009. Milestone anniversary parties, often around Memorial Day at their Tuckahoe Lane home, were celebrated with fanfare even before they could legally marry. Notably, this subseries contains photographs and planning notes from their 15th, 20th, 25th, and 40th anniversaries, including a cake topper frequently reused throughout the years, created from a photograph of Edie and Thea from their 15th anniversary celebration.
    This subseries also includes photographs of their 1993 domestic partnership and 2007 wedding in Toronto, Canada. At the time of their wedding, Thea was 77 and in fragile health, yet the couple's determination to be legally recognized, despite physical and bureaucratic obstacles, underscores the importance of their union. Their travel to Canada and wedding ceremony are documented in this subseries through planning documents, transportation logistics, correspondence, legal paperwork, print and digital photographs, as well as a digital video recording of the ceremony. Their New York Times wedding announcement drafts and photographs further document their public and private commitment. This subseries also contains press coverage surrounding their wedding, and later legal case through clippings and articles, including a controversial 2011 NYU Alumni Magazine cover that drew attention due to the couple's visibility as older married lesbians.
    Also in this subseries are estate planning legal and financial papers, which became especially critical given Edie and Thea's marital status as a same-sex couple prior to federal marriage equality. These records include wills, trusts, correspondence, and financial reports which not only reflect the couple's proactive planning, but also laid groundwork for Windsor's pivotal Supreme Court case, United States v. Windsor.
    This subseries also contains material related to the 2009 documentary by Bless Bless Productions: Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement, released after Thea's death. Items include festival programs and schedules; promotional posters and announcements; and a selection of digital video interview footage that the documentarians, Susan Muska and Gréta Ólafsdottir, created for Windsor.
    Travel played a major role in their relationship, and this subseries includes notes and photographs from their trips, beginning with Suriname in 1965 and continuing to various European countries, St. Barths, Holland, and St. Thomas. The planning notes and correspondence in this subseries reveal, through the years, how each trip became more complex to coordinate as Thea's physical limitations increased and mobility became more difficult.
    - 2 Fifth Avenue Apartment, 1980-2002
      - Renovations / Accessibility Accommodations-Related Booklets, Brochures, Design Floorplans, 1991, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1-2, Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Renovation Floorplans/Blueprints, 1991 (Flat-file-folder 3)
      - Photographs and Negatives -- Interiors, Visit from Judy and Dalia, Fall 1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Slide Images -- Apartment Renovations / Accessibility Accommodations, Visitors, and Party, August-November 1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Photographs -- Apartment Renovation, Friends, Party, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Photographs -- Friends for Dinner, Guests, circa 1990s (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Photographs -- Kitchen and Bathroom Renovation, circa 1990s-2002 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Photographs -- Apartment Interior, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Protest Photographed from Apartment Window, undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - 43 Fifth Avenue Apartment -- Slides and Negatives of Interiors, Party, Portraits of Women, 1969-1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 50s Labor Day Party at Mary Jane Meeker's Photographs, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Address Books and Lists, 1998-2003, undated (Box 22, Folder 3-7)
    - Anniversaries -- Party Planning Material for Multiple Years, 1976-2001 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Anniversaries -- 15th Anniversary Party Photographs, Slides, and Negatives, May 24, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Anniversary Cake Topper Created From 1980 Image of Edie and Thea, 1980-2007 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Anniversaries -- 20th Anniversary Banner and Edie with Trophy Photographs and Negatives, May 1985 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Anniversaries -- 25th Anniversary, May 30, 1990, 2002
      - Scrapbook -- Party Photographs, and Edie's 2002 Short Story "Let the Good Times Roll" (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Party at Herb Cohen's Photographs and Negatives (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Anniversaries -- Party Photographs, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Anniversaries -- 40th Anniversary / East End Gay Organization (EEGO) "Season Opener" Party, May 28, 2005
      - Planning Material (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Print Photographs (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_1
      - Scrapbook Containing Photographs of Edie and Thea Through the Years (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Articles and Press Clippings, 2007-2014 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Articles and Press Clippings -- NYU Alumni Magazine Article and Related, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Artworks -- Purchasing and Artist Information, 1970-1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Bicentennial Party Slide Images, July 4, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Birthday Party for Friend Chuck, and Thea and Edie Swimming in Ocean, circa 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Brigham and Women's Hospital in Boston Trip Documentation, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Budgets and Income/Expense Spreadsheets, 1999-2009; FA_MSS_642_ER_29
    - Charitable Contributions Documentation, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Christmas and Patsy's Graduation Party Photographs and Negatives, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Alphabetical -- Arn and Manfred, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Alphabetical -- Buxbaum, Dev, 1953-1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Alphabetical -- Dean, Nancy, 1967-1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Alphabetical -- Sexton, Elaine, 1996-1997, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Alphabetical -- Spyer, Dick (Thea Cousin), 2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Alphabetical -- Winkler, Judith and Dalia, 1980-2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence Between Edie and Thea, 1965-2005
      - Paper (Box 23, Folder 13, Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Digital File, FA_MSS_642_ER_32
    - Correspondence, Chronological, 1965-2009
      - Paper, 1965-2009 (Box 23, Folder 14, Box 24, Folder 1-5)
      - Digital Files, 2003-2008; FA_MSS_642_ER_30
    - Dinner at Laura and Itsy's -- Slide Images, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Documentary -- Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement -- Correspondence, Promotional Material, Posters, Film Festival Appearance Planning, 2009-2010 (Box 24, Folder 6, Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Documentary -- Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement -- Digital Video Recording of Edie Answering Questions for Screening Event, FA_MSS_642_ER_25
    - Documentary -- Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement -- San Francisco Premiere and Other Film Festivals, June 21 and September 2009
      - Promotional Material (Box 24, Folder 7-9, Box 25, Folder 1-5)
      - Photographs (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Documentary -- Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement -- Film Festivals, 2010
      - Promotional Material (Box 25, Folder 6-14, Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Photographs (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Documentary -- Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement -- Digital Video Recording Interview Clips Sent to Edie by Filmmakers, FA_MSS_642_ER_24
    - Documentary -- Edie & Thea: A Very Long Engagement -- Film Festivals, 2011-2012, 2015
      - Promotional Material (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
      - Digital Images, 2015; FA_MSS_642_ER_31
    - Domestic Partnership, March 1, 1993
      - Documentation and Notes (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Photograph (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Dotty and Sheila's 5th Anniversary Party Photographs, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Marcia Storch Memorial Service Planning, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Edie and Thea at the Beach Photographs, August-September 1969 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Edie and Thea Attending and Hosting Parties Images, 1969-2009
      - Photographs, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)